<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
<item><title>This couple left the city life behind to open a tent and breakfast in Hunza
</title><excerpt>With Khanabadosh Baithak, Ahmed and Baneen curate experiences for travellers who need a break from it all. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:40:39+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Trump's efforts to mediate the Kashmir issue are much needed
</title><excerpt>Historically, the Americans have only woken up and rushed to the region when the two neighbours have been on the brink. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:33+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Extension of Gen Bajwa's tenure — expected but still criticised
</title><excerpt>Surely, the PTI government must try and live up to its own vision of itself as a powerful setup. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:03:20+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>To ensure that the people of Kashmir get the attention they deserve, Pakistan must lead the way
</title><excerpt>This requires Pakistan to take on the difficult issues that it has historically ignored. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:19:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>It is time a new approach is taken towards solving the occupied Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>The role of the mediator and peace builder is critical. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:55:59+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Stocks storm past 30,000-level
</title><excerpt>Bulls rampaged through the stock market for the second day in succession with the KSE-100 index. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:39:19+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>FPCCI reiterates demand for refunds payment
</title><excerpt>“This will lead to achieving the export target set for this fiscal year,” says FPCCI President Daroo Khan Achakzai. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:38:37+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Engro earnings jump 51pc
</title><excerpt>Along with the results, the company announced cash dividend at Rs8 per share. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:37:42+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Spooked Trump insists US economy not in trouble
</title><excerpt>Trump enters the 2020 campaign season facing significant headwinds — except on the economy. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:36:49+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Focus on boosting exports, says Razak
</title><excerpt>Undertaking institutional reforms, documentation of economy, ease of doing business regulation priority for govt. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:36:00+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US sanctions on Huawei bite, but who gets hurt?
</title><excerpt>Chinese technology giant Huawei has yet to feel the full force of US sanctions due to temporary exemptions. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:34:30+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>PSX in throes of ‘correction’: SECP chief
</title><excerpt>Vows no compromise on transparency. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:33:28+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>CAD contracts 73pc in July
</title><excerpt>This was in line with the downward trend witnessed throughout 2018-19 when the deficit stood lower by 31pc. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:32:40+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Second innings for Gen Bajwa
</title><excerpt>The security situation may be a factor, but there have been more pressing reasons for the extension. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:12:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UK ‘concerned’ by reports HK consulate employee detained in China
</title><excerpt>Hong Kong police confirmed they had opened a missing person’s case on Aug 9. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:37:06+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Russia has restarted sharing radiation data, says watchdog
</title><excerpt>In his first comments on the explosion, President Vladimir Putin says that it hasn’t posed any radiation threat.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:41:17+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Facebook launches tool to let users control data flow
</title><excerpt>The tool is to give clients access to their so-called "off-Facebook activity" and give them the option of deleting it. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:32:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Anti-Assad fighters withdraw from key Idlib area
</title><excerpt>Turkey’s Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu says his country has no intention to move the post from Morek.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:29:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Confiscated Beijing skyscraper sold via online auction
</title><excerpt>More than 145,000 internet users followed the auction, but only two bids were cast. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:17:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Desperate migrants jump off rescue ship to reach Italy’s shores
</title><excerpt>Open Arms describes the situation on board as "out of control" and "desperate". 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Concussed Smith ruled out of third Test
</title><excerpt>The 30-year-old was felled by a Jofra Archer bouncer on Saturday in the first innings of the second Test at Lord’s.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:43:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Nai Gaj dam construction cost tripled due to delay, Senate panel told
</title><excerpt>Federal govt blames Sindh govt for financial delays while Sindh claims project revised on account of deferred payments. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:00:56+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Tax notices issued to private schools, tuition centres
</title><excerpt>FBR launches two digital apps for sales tax registration and sales tax invoice verifications.  
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:53:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Singapore to begin public test of driverless buses
</title><excerpt>Consumers will use an app on their phones to book the shuttles. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:05+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Rohingya Muslims in Bangladesh say they don’t want to return home
</title><excerpt>Some Rohingya interviewed by officials on Tuesday say they will not return unless Myanmar gives them citizenship.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:15:07+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India finally shares floodwater discharge data
</title><excerpt>River Sutlej is expected to be in high flood today.   
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:36:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Trump to discuss Kashmir mediation with Modi
</title><excerpt>"I think, we are helping (resolve the tense) situation" between India and Pakistan, says Trump. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:40:54+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Is govt protecting video tape scandal judge, wonders CJP
</title><excerpt>The three-judge Supreme Court bench observes it will decide the fate of the petitions within two or three days. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:33:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Cabinet mulls steps to rein in NAB over complaints by businessmen
</title><excerpt>Dr Firdous Ashiq Awan observes that businessmen are afraid of NAB and are not investing their money. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:26:35+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Three reviews to determine Pakistan’s place on FATF list
</title><excerpt>Pakistan has submitted its compliance report on 27-point action plan committed with the FATF to the Asia-Pacific Group. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:50:52+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>FM Qureshi expresses hope France will 'play its due role' on Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>Briefs French counterpart on "illegal action by India"; French President Macron to discuss Kashmir with Modi this week. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T01:03:29+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US urges India to free detainees, restore rights in occupied Kashmir
</title><excerpt>Trump reiterates offer to mediate the “explosive” situation in Kashmir. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T02:22:47+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Teens swept up in night raids in occupied Kashmir clampdown
</title><excerpt>A widow has a gun put to her head and is told to "keep quiet" by soldiers as they lead her 20-year-old son away. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T23:46:53+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Accountability court rejects Zardari, Talpur's request for 'A' class facilities in jail
</title><excerpt>The court, however, granted approval for various amenities to be installed or brought for use at their own expense. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T21:54:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>6 Indian soldiers killed as Pakistan Army responds to cross-LoC firing: ISPR
</title><excerpt>Firing by Indian troops had killed three civilians, including a seven-year-old boy, in AJK. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T23:31:17+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'IS still strong in some areas': Pompeo says in CBS interview
</title><excerpt>US state secretary talks about IS, Iran, China and North Korea in wide-ranging interviews. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T20:06:50+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan to take Kashmir dispute with India to International Court of Justice
</title><excerpt>“The decision was taken after considering all legal aspects,”  says Foreign Minister Qureshi.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T20:36:26+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'I'm here 24/7': Rohingya youths share their stories on social media
</title><excerpt>Some 30 Rohingya youths have been selected by the World Food Programme for its “Storytellers” project. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T18:28:09+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Firdous seeks nation's support to 'aggressively highlight' Kashmir issue ahead of Modi's UNGA address
</title><excerpt>Pakistan plans to pursue the matter "within the legal framework" if India does not end "war crimes" in occupied Kashmir. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:27:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Hong Kong's leader vows to narrow rifts, but no specifics
</title><excerpt>Chief Executive Carrie Lam offers no concessions to the protest movement. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:12:58+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Huawei dismisses new suspension of 'unjust' US ban
</title><excerpt>"Attempts to suppress Huawei's business won't help the United States achieve technological leadership," Huawei said.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:50:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UK, EU harden their positions on Brexit as G7 approaches
</title><excerpt>Irish premier, after a one-hour call with Johnson, said the Brexit deal wouldn’t be renegotiated. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:48:39+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Italy's political crisis comes to a head as PM tipped to quit
</title><excerpt>Political crisis raises concerns about Italian economy, whose debt ratio at 132% of GDP is second-biggest in eurozone. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:40:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Army chief confirms life sentence for serving major over misuse of authority
</title><excerpt>The officer has been dismissed from service and sent to jail for life, says ISPR statement. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:26:31+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Star batsman Steve Smith ruled out of third Ashes Test after concussion
</title><excerpt>He was unable to play on the fifth and final day on Sunday as he awoke feeling "groggy". 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:24:50+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>PTI's one year: Fixing how we deal with the climate crisis
</title><excerpt>The planet is going to hell in a hand-basket and no one in Pakistan seems to care beyond a broad policy discourse. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:45:46+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'Genocide underway in occupied Kashmir,' warns AJK president
</title><excerpt>Urges UNSC to take up Indian atrocities and Kashmir's right to self determination in an open session. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T15:33:38+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Hasan Ali's pre-wedding photoshoot might be the cutest thing you'll see today
</title><excerpt>That is, until his official wedding photos come out; the ceremony is all set to take place today in Dubai. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T15:28:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: In the year ahead, PTI govt must realise that running the economy requires more than loud claims
</title><excerpt>It took one whole year for the PTI govt to find its feet amid a sinking economy; it must find the rest of its body too. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T14:52:11+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>SC reserves verdict on petitions regarding judge Arshad Malik video scandal
</title><excerpt>Will decide whether to form an inquiry committee or a judicial commission to probe the matter further.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T21:44:30+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Russia, China say US missile test risks sparking an arms race
</title><excerpt>US should "let go of its Cold War mentality", says Chinese foreign ministry spokesman. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:33:20+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Nobel laureate Amartya Sen slams decision to revoke occupied Kashmir's special status
</title><excerpt>"That’s how the British ran the country for 200 years," says Sen in interview with Indian media.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T14:00:06+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Petition submitted in LHC to quash FIRs against Hafiz Saeed, others
</title><excerpt>High court is set to hear the petition submitted by a top JuD leader, Malik Zafar Iqbal, on Thursday. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T18:56:05+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Director Shonali Bose is worried about Zaira Wasim after Article 370 abrogation
</title><excerpt>Because of the communication blockade in Jammu and Kashmir, the Bollywood filmmaker cannot get in touch with the actor. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T13:02:59+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Indian authorities make more arrests in occupied Kashmir to deter protests
</title><excerpt>Primary schools remain deserted as parents worried about the safety of their children keep them at home. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T12:40:54+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Every delay in reporting the crime benefits perpetrators of child sexual abuse
</title><excerpt>Articles 3 and 4 of the Police Order, 2002, mandate the police to protect children.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T12:19:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Besieged Kashmiri neighbourhood in test of wills with India's Modi
</title><excerpt>"If the world won't listen to us too, then what should we do? Pick up guns?" says a 25-year-old resident of Soura. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T11:03:03+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India's Moon probe enters lunar orbit
</title><excerpt>India is seeking to become just the fourth nation to land a spacecraft on the Moon.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T11:24:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Twitter, Facebook accuse China of Hong Kong discord campaign
</title><excerpt>1000 suspended accounts "were deliberately, specifically attempting to sow political discord in HK" says Twitter. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:15:01+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Zakir Naik apologises to Malaysians for racial remarks
</title><excerpt>Naik has permanent residency in Malaysia and several ministers called for his expulsion after his controversial remarks. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T10:50:09+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Is govt protecting video tape scandal judge, wonders CJP
</title><excerpt>The three-judge Supreme Court bench observes it will decide the fate of the petitions within two or three days. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:33:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Nai Gaj dam construction cost tripled due to delay, Senate panel told
</title><excerpt>Federal govt blames Sindh govt for financial delays while Sindh claims project revised on account of deferred payments. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:00:56+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Tax notices issued to private schools, tuition centres
</title><excerpt>FBR launches two digital apps for sales tax registration and sales tax invoice verifications.  
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:53:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India finally shares floodwater discharge data
</title><excerpt>River Sutlej is expected to be in high flood today.   
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:36:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Cabinet mulls steps to rein in NAB over complaints by businessmen
</title><excerpt>Dr Firdous Ashiq Awan observes that businessmen are afraid of NAB and are not investing their money. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:26:35+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Petition submitted in LHC to quash FIRs against Hafiz Saeed, others
</title><excerpt>High court is set to hear the petition submitted by a top JuD leader, Malik Zafar Iqbal, on Thursday. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T18:56:05+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>SC reserves verdict on petitions regarding judge Arshad Malik video scandal
</title><excerpt>Will decide whether to form an inquiry committee or a judicial commission to probe the matter further.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T21:44:30+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>‘CPEC Authority’ being set up for timely completion of projects: PM
</title><excerpt>"The completion of CPEC will not only benefit Pakistan and China, but also the entire region," says the prime minister. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:17:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan to take Kashmir dispute with India to International Court of Justice
</title><excerpt>“The decision was taken after considering all legal aspects,”  says Foreign Minister Qureshi.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T20:36:26+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Extension of Gen Bajwa's tenure — expected but still criticised
</title><excerpt>Surely, the PTI government must try and live up to its own vision of itself as a powerful setup. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:03:20+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Second innings for Gen Bajwa
</title><excerpt>The security situation may be a factor, but there have been more pressing reasons for the extension. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:12:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'Genocide underway in occupied Kashmir,' warns AJK president
</title><excerpt>Urges UNSC to take up Indian atrocities and Kashmir's right to self determination in an open session. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T15:33:38+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan alarmed at Indian attitude over water treaty
</title><excerpt>Vawda says under the accord New Delhi is obligated to provide information about 'extraordinary flood' to Pakistan. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T07:40:49+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>6 Indian soldiers killed as Pakistan Army responds to cross-LoC firing: ISPR
</title><excerpt>Firing by Indian troops had killed three civilians, including a seven-year-old boy, in AJK. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T23:31:17+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Accountability court rejects Zardari, Talpur's request for 'A' class facilities in jail
</title><excerpt>The court, however, granted approval for various amenities to be installed or brought for use at their own expense. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T21:54:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Sindh chief secretary cancels Chinese firm’s garbage-lifting contract over ‘poor performance’
</title><excerpt>Directives have been issued to place additional 4,000 dustbins across the city within three days. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:54:47+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Army chief confirms life sentence for serving major over misuse of authority
</title><excerpt>The officer has been dismissed from service and sent to jail for life, says ISPR statement. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:26:31+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Suspects booked for sectarian violence in last 10 years to be arrested
</title><excerpt>CPO also directed them to ensure daily attendance of all fourth schedulers at the relevant police stations.    
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T09:03:27+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Drive against open littering in city launched officially
</title><excerpt>The Blue Jacket Movement officially commenced at Boat Basin in Clifton on Monday. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:58:52+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>PM calls meeting to take stock of polio situation in light of continuous rise in cases
</title><excerpt>Provincial chief secretaries, international organisations’ representatives to attend. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T09:02:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Plans to celebrate Baba Nanak’s birth anniversary in grand way
</title><excerpt>The Punjab government is keenly emphasising religious tourism. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T09:01:31+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>CAA bifurcation ruffles air traffic controllers’ feathers
</title><excerpt>PM Imran has approved bifurcation of CAA into two divisions on the basis of regulatory functions and airport services. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T09:00:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Hasan Ali's pre-wedding photoshoot might be the cutest thing you'll see today
</title><excerpt>That is, until his official wedding photos come out; the ceremony is all set to take place today in Dubai. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T15:28:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Qaim gets pre-arrest bail in fake accounts case
</title><excerpt>Qaim Ali Shah has been granted pre-arrest interim bail against Rs500,000 surety bonds till August 29.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:10:18+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Every delay in reporting the crime benefits perpetrators of child sexual abuse
</title><excerpt>Articles 3 and 4 of the Police Order, 2002, mandate the police to protect children.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T12:19:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Sindh govt assures PTI lawmakers of probe into police action against protesting nurses
</title><excerpt>The assurance was given during the Sindh Assembly session presided over by Speaker Agha Siraj Durrani. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:57:18+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>This media platform wants to be the premium digital content creator from Pakistan
</title><excerpt>Dot Republic Media already has 6 short films ready to release starring some of your favourite actors 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T10:00:00+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>MPC accuses govt of ‘sellout’ on Kashmir
</title><excerpt>PPP chairman Bilawal Bhutto-Zardari and PML-N president Shahbaz Sharif did not attend the conference. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T07:49:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Furniture, books 'torched' at girls school in Gilgit-Baltistan's Diamer
</title><excerpt>Police find no indication of a short circuit having caused the blaze; officer suspects miscreants' involvement. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T23:18:55+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UAE business tycoon Lootah turns approver against Zardari
</title><excerpt>The top businessman is one of the accused persons in the fake accounts case. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T07:45:40+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Seven-year-old village boy injured in Indian firing dies
</title><excerpt>The civilian death toll in the Indian firing over the last 24 hours has risen to three, officials and residents say. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T22:11:28+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>SJC quashes misconduct reference against Justice Isa for writing letters to president
</title><excerpt>The matter of Justice Isa writing to President Alvi does not constitute misconduct sufficient for his removal: council. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T07:49:37+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>200 accounts suspended over Kashmir reported to Twitter
</title><excerpt>Twitter refutes charge of bias, says no one is above its rules. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:03:47+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Flood alert issued for River Sutlej, Indus after India releases water 'without preschedule'
</title><excerpt>Punjab Chief Minister Usman Buzdar has summoned an emergency meeting to discuss the flood alert for River Sutlej. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T01:36:03+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Kashmir issue on top of today’s multiparty conference agenda
</title><excerpt>Maulana Fazlur Rehman will chair the multiparty conference.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T07:58:46+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Tax notices issued to private schools, tuition centres
</title><excerpt>FBR launches two digital apps for sales tax registration and sales tax invoice verifications.  
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:53:24+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Three reviews to determine Pakistan’s place on FATF list
</title><excerpt>Pakistan has submitted its compliance report on 27-point action plan committed with the FATF to the Asia-Pacific Group. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:50:52+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>CAD contracts 73pc in July
</title><excerpt>This was in line with the downward trend witnessed throughout 2018-19 when the deficit stood lower by 31pc. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:32:40+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Focus on boosting exports, says Razak
</title><excerpt>Undertaking institutional reforms, documentation of economy, ease of doing business regulation priority for govt. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:36:00+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Spooked Trump insists US economy not in trouble
</title><excerpt>Trump enters the 2020 campaign season facing significant headwinds — except on the economy. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:36:49+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>PSX in throes of ‘correction’: SECP chief
</title><excerpt>Vows no compromise on transparency. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:33:28+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Stocks storm past 30,000-level
</title><excerpt>Bulls rampaged through the stock market for the second day in succession with the KSE-100 index. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:39:19+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>FPCCI reiterates demand for refunds payment
</title><excerpt>“This will lead to achieving the export target set for this fiscal year,” says FPCCI President Daroo Khan Achakzai. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:38:37+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Engro earnings jump 51pc
</title><excerpt>Along with the results, the company announced cash dividend at Rs8 per share. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:37:42+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UAE business tycoon Lootah turns approver against Zardari
</title><excerpt>The top businessman is one of the accused persons in the fake accounts case. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T07:45:40+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Huawei dismisses new suspension of 'unjust' US ban
</title><excerpt>"Attempts to suppress Huawei's business won't help the United States achieve technological leadership," Huawei said.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:50:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UK, EU harden their positions on Brexit as G7 approaches
</title><excerpt>Irish premier, after a one-hour call with Johnson, said the Brexit deal wouldn’t be renegotiated. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:48:39+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>‘CPEC Authority’ being set up for timely completion of projects: PM
</title><excerpt>"The completion of CPEC will not only benefit Pakistan and China, but also the entire region," says the prime minister. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:17:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Johnson tells Germany and France: do a Brexit deal
</title><excerpt>"We will be ready to come out on Oct 31 — deal or no deal," Johnson tells reporters in Truro, southwest England.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:45:26+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US sanctions on Huawei bite, but who gets hurt?
</title><excerpt>Chinese technology giant Huawei has yet to feel the full force of US sanctions due to temporary exemptions. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:34:30+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Big industry contracts 3.6pc in FY19
</title><excerpt>In June, the last month of the outgoing fiscal year, the big industry posted a negative growth of 5.05pc. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:21:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Stocks bounce back with a 798-point rally
</title><excerpt>“One swallow does not make a summer,” says a veteran. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:31:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Car sales plunge by 42pc in July
</title><excerpt>The key contributor to this lower production was the closure of production by Honda Atlas Cars. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:22:41+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Tough measures hampering dollar buying
</title><excerpt>Currency dealers said the dollar buying has drastically dropped these days due to strict documentation. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:23:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Regulations for employees’ contributory funds notified
</title><excerpt>The regulations do not apply to a pension funds which are governed under Voluntary Pension Systems Rules 2005.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:28:36+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India eases condition for shadow lenders
</title><excerpt>The non-banking finance companies, also known as shadow lenders, have been battling a credit crunch since 2018. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:26:23+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Greek PM on EU tour to soften fiscal targets
</title><excerpt>Mitsotakis will begin his meetings with a trip to Paris on Thursday. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:24:32+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US grants Huawei another 90 days to buy from American suppliers
</title><excerpt>Authorities say the extension is intended to afford consumers necessary time to transition away from Huawei equipment. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T23:02:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>German economy could continue to shrink: Bundesbank report
</title><excerpt>Central bank of Federal Republic of Germany's report suggests that euro zone's biggest economy is now in a recession. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T16:40:31+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US economists expect recession in 2020 or 2021: survey
</title><excerpt>Economists skeptical about a resolution to Trump's trade wars, although 64pc said a "superficial agreement is possible". 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T21:58:12+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>1,320MW coal-fired Hub power plant commissioned
</title><excerpt>The plant will be set up by the China Power Hub Generation Company (CPHGC) under the CPEC project. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T07:01:51+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>NAB shouldn’t move against bureaucrats on its own: task forces
</title><excerpt>Supervisory bodies recommended at federal, provincial levels to decide if there is sufficient evidence against suspects. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T09:04:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Production from two major gas fields stopped
</title><excerpt>The output from another was drastically cut to ensure smooth flow of expensive, imported LNG into the gas network. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T07:33:02+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Trump dismisses worries of recession, says economy is strong
</title><excerpt>"I don't think we're having a recession," Trump tells reporters. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T11:17:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Inflation may erode PTI’s political capital
</title><excerpt>The government has so far not been able to keep inflation in check even for people in the lowest income group. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:10:46+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Politics creating water shortages
</title><excerpt>Successive governments have allowed direct outlets to canals as political favours. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:39:44+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Pests of pesticide trade
</title><excerpt>‘The only drug-testing laboratory in Punjab’s capital is part of the problem rather than solution’  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T07:02:16+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Millennial money: how to outsmart smartphone scammers
</title><excerpt>Your smartphone is your confidante, your hand-held connection to the world and one of your biggest vulnerabilities. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:11:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>CBS, Viacom to reunite as media giants bulk up for streaming
</title><excerpt>ViacomCBS will be ‘one of only a few companies with the breadth and depth of content'. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:15:43+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>The downside of having a stability programme
</title><excerpt>Pakistan cannot afford a protracted economic slowdown. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:13:14+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Trump to discuss Kashmir mediation with Modi
</title><excerpt>"I think, we are helping (resolve the tense) situation" between India and Pakistan, says Trump. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:40:54+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Rohingya Muslims in Bangladesh say they don’t want to return home
</title><excerpt>Some Rohingya interviewed by officials on Tuesday say they will not return unless Myanmar gives them citizenship.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:15:07+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Anti-Assad fighters withdraw from key Idlib area
</title><excerpt>Turkey’s Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu says his country has no intention to move the post from Morek.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:29:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Desperate migrants jump off rescue ship to reach Italy’s shores
</title><excerpt>Open Arms describes the situation on board as "out of control" and "desperate". 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UK ‘concerned’ by reports HK consulate employee detained in China
</title><excerpt>Hong Kong police confirmed they had opened a missing person’s case on Aug 9. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:37:06+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Singapore to begin public test of driverless buses
</title><excerpt>Consumers will use an app on their phones to book the shuttles. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:05+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Russia has restarted sharing radiation data, says watchdog
</title><excerpt>In his first comments on the explosion, President Vladimir Putin says that it hasn’t posed any radiation threat.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:41:17+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Confiscated Beijing skyscraper sold via online auction
</title><excerpt>More than 145,000 internet users followed the auction, but only two bids were cast. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:17:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>US urges India to free detainees, restore rights in occupied Kashmir
</title><excerpt>Trump reiterates offer to mediate the “explosive” situation in Kashmir. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T02:22:47+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Facebook launches tool to let users control data flow
</title><excerpt>The tool is to give clients access to their so-called "off-Facebook activity" and give them the option of deleting it. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:32:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India finally shares floodwater discharge data
</title><excerpt>River Sutlej is expected to be in high flood today.   
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:36:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>FM Qureshi expresses hope France will 'play its due role' on Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>Briefs French counterpart on "illegal action by India"; French President Macron to discuss Kashmir with Modi this week. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T01:03:29+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'IS still strong in some areas': Pompeo says in CBS interview
</title><excerpt>US state secretary talks about IS, Iran, China and North Korea in wide-ranging interviews. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T20:06:50+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Trump's efforts to mediate the Kashmir issue are much needed
</title><excerpt>Historically, the Americans have only woken up and rushed to the region when the two neighbours have been on the brink. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:16:33+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>UK, EU harden their positions on Brexit as G7 approaches
</title><excerpt>Irish premier, after a one-hour call with Johnson, said the Brexit deal wouldn’t be renegotiated. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:48:39+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan to take Kashmir dispute with India to International Court of Justice
</title><excerpt>“The decision was taken after considering all legal aspects,”  says Foreign Minister Qureshi.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T20:36:26+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Hong Kong's leader vows to narrow rifts, but no specifics
</title><excerpt>Chief Executive Carrie Lam offers no concessions to the protest movement. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:12:58+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Huawei dismisses new suspension of 'unjust' US ban
</title><excerpt>"Attempts to suppress Huawei's business won't help the United States achieve technological leadership," Huawei said.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:50:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>To ensure that the people of Kashmir get the attention they deserve, Pakistan must lead the way
</title><excerpt>This requires Pakistan to take on the difficult issues that it has historically ignored. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:19:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>It is time a new approach is taken towards solving the occupied Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>The role of the mediator and peace builder is critical. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T07:55:59+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Italy's political crisis comes to a head as PM tipped to quit
</title><excerpt>Political crisis raises concerns about Italian economy, whose debt ratio at 132% of GDP is second-biggest in eurozone. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:40:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Russia, China say US missile test risks sparking an arms race
</title><excerpt>US should "let go of its Cold War mentality", says Chinese foreign ministry spokesman. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:33:20+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Indian authorities make more arrests in occupied Kashmir to deter protests
</title><excerpt>Primary schools remain deserted as parents worried about the safety of their children keep them at home. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T12:40:54+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Zakir Naik apologises to Malaysians for racial remarks
</title><excerpt>Naik has permanent residency in Malaysia and several ministers called for his expulsion after his controversial remarks. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T10:50:09+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>India's Moon probe enters lunar orbit
</title><excerpt>India is seeking to become just the fourth nation to land a spacecraft on the Moon.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T11:24:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Twitter, Facebook accuse China of Hong Kong discord campaign
</title><excerpt>1000 suspended accounts "were deliberately, specifically attempting to sow political discord in HK" says Twitter. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:15:01+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Aid cut improved ties with Pakistan: Trump
</title><excerpt>"So, what happened: I cut back $1.3 billion. We have a better relationship now," says Trump. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T17:48:49+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>'I'm here 24/7': Rohingya youths share their stories on social media
</title><excerpt>Some 30 Rohingya youths have been selected by the World Food Programme for its “Storytellers” project. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T18:28:09+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>‘Some things’ about Afghanistan to be announced soon: Trump
</title><excerpt>Trump, however, did not offer details of this announcement.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:23:56+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Malaysia quizzes Zakir Naik as pressure mounts
</title><excerpt>Zakir Naik left India in 2016 and moved to largely Muslim Malaysia, where he was granted permanent residency. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:28:06+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Sudan’s Bashir ‘got $90m from Saudi royals’, official tells court
</title><excerpt>The former president sat in a metal cage wearing a traditional white gown in the Khartoum court. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:25:14+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Air strikes target Turkish convoy in Syria
</title><excerpt>The Turkish Defence Ministry gives no word on Turkish casualties. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:29:02+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Trump stresses need to reduce India-Pakistan tension in phone calls to PM Imran, Modi
</title><excerpt>"A tough situation, but good conversations!" says Trump. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T18:37:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Director Shonali Bose is worried about Zaira Wasim after Article 370 abrogation
</title><excerpt>Because of the communication blockade in Jammu and Kashmir, the Bollywood filmmaker cannot get in touch with the actor. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T13:02:59+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Global network’s nuclear sensors went offline after mystery blast
</title><excerpt>The Russian Defence Ministry, which operates the two stations, did not immediately reply to a request for comment.
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:39:45+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Concussed Smith ruled out of third Test
</title><excerpt>The 30-year-old was felled by a Jofra Archer bouncer on Saturday in the first innings of the second Test at Lord’s.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-21T08:43:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Star batsman Steve Smith ruled out of third Ashes Test after concussion
</title><excerpt>He was unable to play on the fifth and final day on Sunday as he awoke feeling "groggy". 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T16:24:50+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Azhar Mahmood feels coaching staff deserved chance to clarify position
</title><excerpt>Azhar admitted fast bowler Mohammad Hasnain’s selection in the World Cup squad was a mistake. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:41:53+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Sharjeel apologises as PCB waives ban sentence
</title><excerpt>Sharjeel was suspended from national and international cricket for five years by the PCB in 2017. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:42:36+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Mandatory neck guards not far off after Smith blow
</title><excerpt>Australia have been at the forefront of pressing for better safety measures for players. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:43:23+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Archer’s sensational debut changes complexion of Ashes series
</title><excerpt>The times on the speed gun kept on rising. 
 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:40:17+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Medvedev breaks into top five at last
</title><excerpt>The 23-year-old became the first Russian player in history to win a Masters title. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:35:02+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Prince Albert outpaces rivals to clinch Jashn-e-Azadi Cup
</title><excerpt>The son of Denmark-bred sire Chapter One backed at 3-2 beat filly Sparking by two lengths. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:37:58+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>PSG leave out Neymar again on way to shock Rennes defeat
</title><excerpt>The visitors were gifted the opener when Edinson Cavani tapped in after a defensive mix-up. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:38:23+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Leipzig crush Union 4-0 to spoil newcomers’ Bundesliga debut
</title><excerpt>RB Leipzig spoiled hosts Union Berlin’s .Bundesliga debut on Sunday. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-20T08:39:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Olympic gold medallist Zakir Hussain passes away at 85
</title><excerpt>Hussain's funeral prayers will be carried out at his home town in Wah Cantt. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T14:36:36+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Mandatory neck guards 'not far away' after Smith felled by Archer
</title><excerpt>Australia have been at the forefront of pressing for better safety measures after the death of Phillip Hughes. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T13:38:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Archer, Stokes give England advantage in Lord’s Test
</title><excerpt>Australia were struggling at 46-2 in their second innings at tea on a compelling final day of the second Test. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:31:25+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>ACA blasts English fans for booing injured Smith
</title><excerpt>Smith was eventually able to walk off the field for concussion checks to a standing ovation. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:34:35+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Afghanistan board suspends Shahzad for one year
</title><excerpt>Shahzad’s suspension stems from his breach of policy that requires players to seek permission before travelling abroad. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:36:03+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Chelsea held by Leicester, Sheffield United win
</title><excerpt>Chelsea raced into a quick lead when the 20 year-old Mount stole the ball from a dallying Ndidi. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T08:32:08+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Australia hold out for second Test draw against England as concussed Smith sidelined
</title><excerpt>Australia were 154-6 at the close, given a stiff target of 267 in 48 overs when England captain Joe Root declared. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-19T00:37:49+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>New Zealand rugby team says World Cup more important than top ranking
</title><excerpt>“We just need to get ourselves in the right frame of mind to go to the World Cup and win that,” says team coach. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-18T16:19:22+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Sri Lanka may consider  playing a Test on Pakistan  soil in October
</title><excerpt>According to a report by *ESPNcricinfo*, the security delegation gave SLC “very positive feedback” upon its return. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-18T09:59:13+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Liverpool extend perfect start, Aubameyang inspires Arsenal as Pukki hits hat-trick
</title><excerpt>The Reds’ confident start to the season puts pressure on champions Manchester City to respond with a second win. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-18T10:03:10+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Kaleemullah, Nasir Ali to join PHF selection committee
</title><excerpt>The PHF had announced a four-member committee headed by Olympian Manzoor Junior. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-18T10:05:37+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Smith holds firm as Australia frustrate England in second Ashes Test
</title><excerpt>Australia were 155-5 at lunch, having lost just one wicket in the session; hosts England scored 258 in first innings. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T18:10:19+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>BD bring in Domingo as new head coach
</title><excerpt>The 44-year-old has agreed to a two-year term with the BCB and is expected to arrive in Dhaka on Wednesday. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-18T10:12:48+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Foreign coaches cannot improve Pakistan cricket: Sarfraz Nawaz
</title><excerpt>Former pacer also wants PCB to allow departmental teams to continue playing at least in one-day and T20 events. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:04:06+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Australia slump before rain cuts short play in Lord’s Test
</title><excerpt>Australia lost three wickets for 11 runs en route to slumping to 80-4. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:00:35+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Battling Watling revives NZ hopes
</title><excerpt>New Zealand, who trailed Sri Lanka by 18 runs in the first innings, finished on 195-7. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:00:53+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Big win sets Wolves up for Europa League playoff with Torino
</title><excerpt>The winner of the home and away legs on August 22 and 29 will progress to the group stage.   
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:04:33+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Shastri wins close race to stay as India head coach
</title><excerpt>Former India players Lalchand Rajput and Robin Singh were also short-listed candidates.   
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:02:02+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Back problem hampers Morgan’s desire for second World Cup success
</title><excerpt>The 32-year-old Irishman had problems with his back during the drawn-out World Cup campaign. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-17T10:02:47+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Misbah likely to get dual role of chief selector  and head coach
</title><excerpt>PCB set to introduce a new model of domestic cricket soon. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-16T09:37:09+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Hazlewood strikes on Ashes return to leave England wobbling
</title><excerpt>After rain washed out Wednesday’s first day, Australia captain Tim Paine decided to field first after winning the toss. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-16T09:42:46+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Spinner Patel stars as SL lose ground in Galle Test
</title><excerpt>Sri Lanka trail New Zealand by 22 runs with three first-innings wickets remaining. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-16T09:44:14+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>SA cricket director seeks Guardiola inspiration
</title><excerpt>Nkwe, 36, tells a press conference on Thursday that he was a big fan of Manchester City manager Guardiola. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-16T09:47:28+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>King Kohli leads India to victory and overshadows Gayle swansong
</title><excerpt>While Kohli illuminated the gathering gloom in at the end of the match, it was Gayle who stole the show at the start.  
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-15T10:36:27+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Liverpool beats Chelsea on penalties to lift Super Cup
</title><excerpt>Adrian makes crucial save with his leg to deny Tammy Abraham and give his team a 5-4 win. 
    </excerpt><time>2019-08-15T10:31:36+05:00</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Trump's efforts to mediate the Kashmir issue are much needed
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Editorial: Extension of Gen Bajwa's tenure — expected but still criticised
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>It is time a new approach is taken towards solving the occupied Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>This couple left the city life behind to open a tent and breakfast in Hunza
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>The downside of having a stability programme
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Patriotism vs commercial interests
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Flood alert issued for River Sutlej, Indus after India releases water 'without preschedule'
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Trump stresses need to reduce India-Pakistan tension in phone calls to PM Imran, Modi
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Modi’s next move
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan takes up suspension of accounts 'posting in support of Kashmir' with Twitter, Facebook
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>World must wake up to India’s nuke threat, says PM
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Army chief Gen Bajwa's tenure extended for another 3 years
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>'World must seriously consider safety, security of India's nuclear arsenal in control of fascist Modi'
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>UNSC Kashmir moot gives lie to Indian claim
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Patriotism vs commercial interests
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>'UNSC, OIC have responded positively to Pakistan's call,' says FM Qureshi
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Flood alert issued for River Sutlej, Indus after India releases water 'without preschedule'
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Trump stresses need to reduce India-Pakistan tension in phone calls to PM Imran, Modi
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Modi’s next move
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan takes up suspension of accounts 'posting in support of Kashmir' with Twitter, Facebook
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>World must wake up to India’s nuke threat, says PM
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>The unspoken reality
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Trump stresses need to reduce India-Pakistan tension in phone calls to PM Imran, Modi
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Modi’s next move
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Pakistan alarmed at Indian attitude over water treaty
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>FM Qureshi expresses hope France will 'play its due role' on Kashmir issue
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Aid cut improved ties with Pakistan: Trump
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>200 accounts suspended over Kashmir reported to Twitter
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
<item><title>Nobel laureate Amartya Sen slams decision to revoke occupied Kashmir's special status
</title><excerpt>None</excerpt><time>None</time></item>
</items>